{
    "id": "7cd1e150d3dc4b4ea3958a54dfbcb4f8",
    "title": "Grammar Exercise | Prepositions",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "This area is backward ……………….. most aspects.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e6fbdc2743ee430eb567603b9b1027ee"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t think we can count ……………….. him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b2c41a6b81c449bc816057de84c8fd1f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you believe …………………. ghosts?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1cf2824a72b340cab83b57788b79fd9d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Beware ……………… dogs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "about",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f0c43e68c8294dcab5434f724c26d5b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The Emperor brought ………………. many reforms during his reign.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "about",
                "up",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a69e494ad48342f38640c4059c825f1b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Are you interested …………….. psychology?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "for",
                "about",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ad436ee5985f40f293b30c3f7e9cad20"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am very bad ..................... remembering names.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "feee8ba2522440258a8e1a0ad0bbb31a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Susie went green ……………….. envy when she saw my new car.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "at",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4cd279af4d7445b18fea5a1492ea23cf"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher congratulated the boys ……………….. their performance.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bedde20b57e7494a82865c9b2b16e479"
        },
        {
            "question": "Suddenly he complained …………….. chest pain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "of",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2fa38faff3184d9ab9dce47863aece14"
        }
    ]
}